camillestyles.com 2019-04-13

# Privacy Policy - Camille Styles

_Last updated on February 11, 2019._

This Privacy Policy governs the manner in which Camille Styles, Inc. (“we”, “us”, “our” or similar pronouns) collects, uses, maintains and discloses information collected from users (each, a “User”) of camillestyles.com (“Site”). This privacy policy applies only to the Site and all products and services offered by Camille Styles, Inc. (including, without limitation, both mobile and online versions of our web sites, and also applies to your use of all features, applications, content, downloads and other services that we make available through these web sites and/or that post a link to this Privacy Policy (collectively, referred to herein as the “Site”), regardless of how you access or use the Site, whether via personal computers, mobile devices or otherwise. This Privacy Policy does not apply to our data collection activities offline or otherwise outside of our Service (unless otherwise stated below).

WHEN YOU ACCESS OR USE THE WEBSITE, OR OTHERWISE PROVIDE ANY INFORMATION TO US, YOU AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, INCLUDING THE MANNER IN WHICH WE USE YOUR INFORMATION. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, OR TO ANY CHANGES WE MAY SUBSEQUENTLY MAKE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU MUST IMMEDIATELY STOP USING THE WEBSITE OR OTHERWISE PROVIDING ANY INFORMATION TO US.

The Website may contain links to other websites. This Privacy Policy does not apply to information collected on or through any such third party websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of such third parties or the content of their websites. Such third parties may have their own privacy policies and you should review those privacy policies to determine their privacy practices.

**Personal identification information**  
We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, subscribe to the newsletter, fill out a form, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, phone number, and other information about them or their business or organization. Users may, however, visit our Site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from Users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain Site related activities. Information collected may be stored on our computer hardware or the hardware of our third party service providers.

**Non-personal identification information**  
We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include but is not limited to the browser specifications, the type of computer and technical information about Users’ means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system and the Internet service providers utilized and other similar information.

**Opting In**  
By submitting your e-mail address to us, you opt-in to receiving e-mail from us. You may opt-out of receiving further e-mail by contacting us via email or following the directions in any email or elsewhere on this site. If you wish to opt-out at any point from our emails enter your email address here.

**Opting Out**  
If you want to be removed from our marketing list and do not want us to send you e-mail, postal mail or other messages about our products and services, you can opt out. To do so, please select unsubscribe on the email communication.

California Civil Code Section 1798.83 permits California residents to request certain information regarding our disclosure of such residents’ personal information to third parties for such third parties’ direct marketing purposes. To make such a request, please e-mail us at info@camillestyles.com.

**How we use collected information**  
Camille Styles collects and uses Users’ personal information for the following purposes:

_To personalize and improve user experience_  
We may use information to better respond to your individual needs and customize your experience. Or in the aggregate, to understand how our Users as a group use the services and resources provided on our Site.

_To improve our Site_  
We continually strive to improve our website offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you.

_To improve customer service_  
Your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs.

_To administer content, promotion, survey or other Site feature_  
We may send Users information they agreed to receive about topics we think will be of interest to them.

_To provide services_  
We may use the information Users provide about themselves, their business or organization to provide the services requested. These services may include services provided by third parties.

**Sharing your personal information**  
We may use the information we collect to identify the parties with whom we are dealing and to provide customized information and offers of products and services. While we do not currently use third party services that display customized content and advertising provided by us, we may do so in the future. We may also use the information for statistical and/or marketing purposes, to improve our technologies, to provide information about our company and to deliver advertising and promotional information from our partners and third party vendors. We may track your use of the Website over time for the purpose of, among other things, enhancing your experience on the Website and providing marketing messages, promotions, offers of products and services and other content which we think may be of specific interest to you.

We reserve the right to share, rent, sell or otherwise disclose the information we collect from you to third parties. We may also share your information with certain third parties in other circumstances, including when complying with legal process, preventing fraud or imminent harm and/or ensuring the security of our network and services. We may also use the information you provide to market products and services to you. We may obtain your information through third parties by virtue of advertisements placed by us on websites maintained by those third parties. We will collect and/or share certain of your information with third parties for the purposes of fulfilling orders for products or services placed by you and for providing you with newsletters or other communications.

When we use third parties to assist us in collecting and/or processing your personal information, we typically request that they comply with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures. However, we make no representation or warranty that such third parties will comply with any such request.

We may provide you with direct access to functionality from other third parties, including Facebook, Twitter, Instagram, YouTube, Pinterest, Spotify, advertising networks and others. The placement of social media widgets, or advertising units on the Website may permit these third parties to see information about you and your activities via cookies, web beacons and other technologies they place and/or access on your browser or device, even if you do not interact with them.

**Do Not Track**  
When you use the Website, we may receive “do not track” requests from you, whether via signals from web browsers or other mechanisms. At this time, we do not respond to such “do not track” requests, although we may choose to do so in the future.

**Use of Web Technologies**  
_Cookies_  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user’s computer for record keeping purposes. We use cookies on the Website. We may link the information we store in cookies to personally identifiable information that you submit while on the Website. We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. A session ID cookie expires when a browser is closed. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on the Website. You can remove the persistent cookies by following the directions provided in your internet browser’s “help” file. If you reject cookies, you may still use the Website but your ability to use some areas of the Website may be limited.

_Tracking Pixels_  
We employ a software technology called tracking pixels (a/k/a web beacons/web bugs/clear gifs) that enables us to better manage the content on the Website by informing us what content is effective. Tracking pixels are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies, and are used to track the online movements of visitors to a website. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user’s computer hard drive, tracking pixels are embedded invisibly on website pages and are about the size of the period at the end of a sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by tracking pixels to your personally identifiable information.

We use tracking pixels in our HTML-based e-mails to let us know which e-mails have been opened by recipients. This allows us to gauge the effectiveness of certain communications and the effectiveness of our marketing campaigns. If you would like to opt-out of these e-mails, please see the “Opting Out” section of this Privacy Policy below.

_Log Files_  
As is true of most websites, we gather information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the Website, to track the movements of users around the Website and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole.

_Communications_  
Based upon the personally identifiable information that you provide to us, we may send you a welcome e-mail. We will also communicate with you in response to your inquiries, to provide any services you request, to provide newsletters or other updates that you request. If, at any time, you no longer want us to contact you by e-mail and/or receive our e-mail subscriptions, editorial e-mails and advertorial e-mails, you may opt out.

We may send you e-mails that contain advertising or other content sponsored by third party retailers or businesses (“advertorial e-mails”). The content is marked in partnership with a third party retailer and paid for by our sponsors and does not reflect the opinions of our editorial staff. If you prefer not to receive these e-mails, you may opt-out as provided in the “Opting Out” section of this Privacy Policy below. We send advertorial e-mails on behalf of the third party sponsors. We do not share your personally identifiable information with such sponsors, except as otherwise provided in this Privacy Policy, but we may sell or share aggregate, non-personal information with such sponsors for any legally permissible purpose.

**International Users**  
Camille Styles is based in the United States, with our servers and offices headquartered in the United States. Please be aware that information you provide to us or that we obtain as a result of your use of the Website may be processed and transferred to, and be subject to the laws of, the United States. The privacy and data protection laws in the United States may not be equivalent to similar laws in your country of residence. By using the Website or by providing us with your information, you consent to the collection, transfer, storage and processing of information to and within the United States. If our cookies or other software detects IP addresses located in a country outside the United States, we reserve the right to deny access to any and all of our services.

**Changes to this privacy policy**  
We may modify, amend or otherwise change this privacy policy at any time in our sole discretion, without your consent and without prior notice. If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

**Performance; No Guarantee**  
While we take all reasonable measures to comply with this policy, we cannot ensure that your information will be 100% secure due to hackers, disgruntled employees, acts of God, etc. We will exercise commercially reasonable efforts to maintain compliance with the terms of this privacy policy. This is not a contractual agreement to provide any level of security for your data as breaches of personal information may occur on any system in spite of best practices and best efforts. We commit to provide timely notification of any customers whose information is involved in any information leak or breach.

**Advertising Privacy Statement  
**This Site is affiliated with AdThrive, LLC (“AdThrive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site.  AdThrive uses standard and widely-available tools for the placement and serving of ads, including those provided by Google, Inc. and its affiliates. We publish interest-based advertisements on the Site; that is, ads that are tailored to reflect your interests. To help understand your interests, AdThrive, Google and our other advertising partners will track your behavior on our website and on other websites across the Internet using cookies.

A cookie is a file containing an identifier (a string of letters and numbers) that is sent by a web server to a web browser and is stored by the browser. The identifier is then sent back to the server each time the browser requests a page from the server. Cookies may be either “persistent” cookies or “session” cookies: a persistent cookie will be stored by a web browser and will remain valid until its set expiry date, unless deleted by the user before the expiry date; a session cookie, on the other hand, will expire at the end of the user session, when the web browser is closed.  Cookies do not typically contain any information that personally identifies a user, but personal information that we store about you may be linked to the information stored in and obtained from cookies.

By using this Site, you consent to the use of such cookies and the sharing of data captured by such cookies with AdThrive, Google, and our other third party partners. You can view, delete or add interest categories associated with your browser by visiting: [https://adssettings.google.com](https://adssettings.google.com/). You can also opt out of the network cookie using those settings or using the Network Advertising Initiative’s multi-cookie opt-out mechanism at: [http://optout.networkadvertising.org](http://optout.networkadvertising.org/). However, these opt-out mechanisms themselves use cookies, and if you clear the cookies from your browser your opt-out will not be maintained.

For European Economic Area Residents

If you reside in a country in the European Economic Area (EEA), then under the GDPR and applicable data protection laws you have the rights, among other things, to access your personal data, have us erase it, and/or restrict its further processing.  If you wish to access or delete your personal data (if any) maintained by us or AdThrive related to advertising on the Site, you can contact us at info@camillestyles.com ** ** and contact AdThrive at [info@adthrive.com](mailto:info@adthrive.com). If you wish to see a list of the advertising partners we work with or change which of those partners track your behavior using cookies, click the ad preferences link at the bottom of the site. (Available in the EU.)

**Contacting us**  
If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us:  
Camille Styles, Inc.  
1005 West Avenue  
Austin, Texas 78701  
info@camillestyles.com
